http://www.wesellroll-n-lockbymailorder.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com gathers aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.
Usage Tracking
WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser). WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com uses tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
Cookies
WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com may use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.
Sharing of Information
WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us better understand our audience’s demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com may share the information with our sister companies.
Your Consent
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by WeSellRoll-N-LockByMailOrder.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Information
Site Links
Home
About Us
Contact Us
Roll-N-Lock Products
Roll-N-Lock® M-Series™
Roll-N-Lock® E-Series™
Home | About Us | Contact Us | Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | Links
